[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Are we all just watching the final vestiges of this race when actually Romney has already crossed the line?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "RB", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Well, I can tell you that both Obama and the Romney campaigns think that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "But say he lost in Pennsylvania, doesn't his dignity then say he must pull out then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "That's a great point.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pennsylvania"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "So Evan, what was your conclusion so far about this race in terms of its merit as a political challenge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Well, it is entertaining, and if you read the book, you'll see it's for the camps very tense and scary.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Evan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike Allen"]}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Well, if Mike Allen reports it, of course it's true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "NN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Don't you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "I think that, but listen, there's a fight within the Romney campaign because some people do want him to come out and show a more human side.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "I mean he's a pretty good guy when it comes to basic normal human values, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "No, that's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Louisiana"]}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "How do you come back from this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "Well, look, I mean, two weeks ago I was here with you and you were talking about our big wins and then we went on to win Louisiana and we've won already 11 states.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "If Mitt Romney kicks Rick Santorum's butt in Pennsylvania, in his own backyard, isn't that game over?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Well, let's put it this way.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Rick Santorum"], "LOCATION": ["Pennsylvania"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "How many times did he come last in these primary battles now and retain credibility as a candidate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Well, Barack Obama himself called out Newt by name today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "The question becomes who backs who and surely all the polls tell you and all the momentum tells you that Newt would have to throw support behind Rick Santorum, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", "WP", "CC", "RB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "That's what all the pundit say, but Newt Gingrich has been counted out before and we're going to have a three-week lull now with -- I think for some it's a law, for others it's an opportunity to have a conversation to make sure that we continue to unify at least a message, at least in principle, if not in process at the moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Santorum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "What is the roadmap ahead for the Romney campaign?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "You know what, it's a power of delegates, it's the power of wins, it's to cut the burn rail a little bit on the spending.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "At what point do you think other candidates should pull out of this race?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "You know, Piers, it's not my call.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Santorum", "Santorum"]}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "How does he rebuild trust in the female vote?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "I think that's more of a function of the Santorum campaign quite frankly, and the Democrats are using some of Senator Santorum's verbiage to their electoral advantage, to their partisan advantage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Is he champing it a bit to get in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I think a little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "And what do you think, as one of his friends, he needs to do to stop making those kind of mistakes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "The media tends to play you the Etch A Sketch stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Are you feeling like the wedding is on its way here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Well, I've always seen this as almost like a prize fight, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Is this feasible or has the horse bolted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Yes, the horse has bolted.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "How is he going to turn around the perception of himself in tough economic times that he's simply out of touch with the average American?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Well, I think he needs to do a better job at fighting back against the media.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "You know, is he just too nice a guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Well, I think those are all great things, but I think there's a difference between being nasty and campaigning dirty which I think you could argue that he kind of does, but also being an aggressive campaigner.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Which camp are you -- and I know you like Romney, but if you're President Obama, are you feeling vulnerable or confident tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "Well, I think, Piers, we've seen that President Obama is having a little bit of a mini meltdown.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney", "Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "How do you deal with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Well, the White House is hoping in terms of unemployment that the trend is going in the right direction for them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 536, "question": "Where is your money going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "You know, I'm not a -- I'm not a gambling man, but I do think --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", ":", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "So he's a skilled man, he's a good businessman, he's intelligent, but he's got a real uphill battle, doesn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "The conventional wisdom surely right now is that Romney is a pretty weak nominee, that -- but these things that we saw go back and forth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Who should be Mitt Romney's running mate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Cantor.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rubio"]}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Ben?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "Very likely to be Rubio.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Carol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Rubio.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Why is it so crazy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "Well, he -- you know, he didn't do the Hillary --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "What about Sarah Palin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "ORGAN: She's better this time than last time, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]